问题有三种类型：yes-no、either-or，以及五个 W 问题。
There are three types of questions, yes-no, either-or, and the five W questions.
每一种都有不同的曲调模式，所以即使你没听清所有
They each have a different inflection pattern, so even if you don't catch all
即使没听清所有词，也能判断问题类型。五个 W 问题是：
the words, you can still tell what type of question it was. The five W questions are
who、what、where、when、why，以及 how。正如你在前面的问答中听到的，
who, what, where, when, and why, and how. As you heard in the question response
在前面的例子里，Where's the book？It's on the table。语调会上扬，
above, where's the book? It's on the table. The inflection goes up on the
疑问句上扬，陈述句下降。像 would you like tea or coffee？这样的问句，
question and down on the statement. A query like, would you like tea or coffee?
可能是 either-or 问题：Tea？Coffee？也可能是 yes-no 问题：Would you
Could be an either or question. Tea? Coffee? Or a yes no question. Would you
一个经典但可能并不真实的故事说明了
like tea or coffee? Hot beverage? A classic, probably apocryphal story spells
误解问题类型会带来什么后果。
out the consequences of misinterpreting the question type. An immigrant was
通过埃利斯岛时，被问到当时的标准问题：
passing through Ellis Island and was asked the then standard question, are you
你是否计划用武力或暴力推翻美国？
planning to overthrow the United States by force or violence? The man pondered deeply
那人沉思片刻，试探性地回答：by force？当然，他没被允许入境，
for a moment and tentatively replied, by force? Of course, he was not let in, as
因为唯一可接受的答案是 no。
the only acceptable answer was no.